[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
Now, so far,
目前为止
we've really just talked about how do you build a machine learning model using data?
我们说到了你如何用数据来建立机器学习的模型
How do you measure its quality?
那么如何来衡量质量呢？
And how do you understand whether it's working or not?
你如何去理解模型是否有效？
But that's not enough to build an intelligent application.
所以说 光光建立起一个模型还远远不够
When you build an intelligent application, you want to take all that you learn and
当你建立起一个人工智能 你想要的是
then really put it in front of,
介绍给你公司的客户
say the customers of your company who are going to your website to buy a product.
那些去你的网站购买你的产品的客户
So what does the process actually look like?
这个过程像什么呢？
There are many different aspects associated with it.
涉及到方方面面
This is what we call model deployment, where we're taking the model and
这就是我们所谓的模型部署
we allow it to serve predictions in real time.
我们把模型用来做实时预测
We'll talk more about that.
我们还会继续说到
Then we'll talk about how do we evaluate that model to make sure what we did and
我们会提到如何去衡量模型 来保证
offline as we train the model is still good in the long run as we're using it.
我们所设计的模型 在长期来说仍是有效的
Then we have to think about all the management pieces.
如果你想到了管理
How do make sure the model is still good, how do we replace it when the model
你如何保证模型仍然有效 我们如何去替换来提升模型
improves, and how do we react to measurements that we make,
对于我们的评测结果 如何反应
which are actually the metrics that we monitor over time to try to understand
这些都是我们需要监测的内容
whether our models are still good or it's time to relearn them from data.
这样才能了解我们的模型是否有效 和知道模型能否从数据得到新的训练
Now all these pieces are really coming together.
现在所有的内容都来了
They're not just individual, separated ones, but interacting pieces that we need
并不是单独的 分散开来的 每一项内容都会有联系
to understand deeply and create a cycle of improvement of the models that we have.
我们需要建立起一个完整的能够提升模型的循环系统
So let's start with the first one.
让我们从第一个开始
Let's start with deployment piece.
部署部分
Now consider the following setup.
思考以下的设置
You're building a really cool new kind of product recommending system, and
你要建立的是一个新的产品推荐系统
you're using a bunch of data with millions of product reviews and users.
你用了百万级别的产品点评和用户喜好的数据
And you want to take the model that you learned on your laptop, in your desktop or
你想要让你从你笔记本或者台式机
in the big cluster of machines.
或者大型计算机中训练得出的模型
And deploy it on the website that really interacts with your users.
把他部署到网页上 能够使它和你的用户进行真正的交互
What does that look like?
这就像是什么呢?
Well that whole system starts with some historical data.
就像是使用着历史数据的整个系统
Some data that you've collected about the users of your system,
你收集的系统中用户的数据
the reviews they've written, what preferences they have.
用户写下的点评 他们的爱好
And we take that data and we feed it to train a model like we saw in
我们将要使用这些数据 来训练模型
the recommender systems module that Emily taught, that process
就像Emily之前在推荐系统那个模块中已经教过的
with historical data is usually done in what's called a batch offline setting.
使用历史数据叫做批量离线设置
You learn a model, say on your desktop machine or in a cluster, and
你在你笔记本或者大型计算机中学习了模型
then take the model and deploy it, for example, in the cloud, so
并把它在云上面进行部署
that you can do what's called serving predictions.
你所做的是服务器预测
This is the online, real time part of the system.
这是线上的 实时的
So, for example, if you have a website, if this is what we're serving for,
如果你有一个网站 如果他是我们服务的网站
the website is going to give me information about my users,
网站会给我关于用户的信息
what they're doing right now, what pages they looked,
用户们现在在做什么 他们在浏览哪个页面
what products they're thinking about buying.
他们想要买什么产品
And then from that, we're going to serve predictions in real time to say oh,
所有的这些 都会用来做实时预测
check out this giraffe chew toy.
还记得之前的长劲鹿玩具吗
Remember that?
你们记得吗？
Check that out as this might be something that you want to buy right now.
假设这是你现在想买的东西
Now the user sees that giraffe offering and they may or may not buy the giraffe.
用户看到了长劲鹿 他们可能会买也可能不会买这个长颈鹿
That's the kind of feedback we're going to get back from the system.
这是我们会从系统中得到的反馈
Did the user buy it or did they not buy it?
是否这个用户真的买了产品
That's going to influence both, our real time decisions.
这会影响到我们的实时决定
And go back to historical data and really be collected in the long run so
和回顾历史数据 并且收集到长期的训练模型中
that we can improve our model as we collect more and more data from the world.
这样我们就能够不断地从现实生活中收集数据从而提升我们的模型
So that's what holistic deployment system for machine learning might look like.
这也就是机器学习的全盘部署系统
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community